

#### **PERSONAL**

Name & Surname
Oguljemal Yusupova

**Address**Pendik

**Number** 905526053712

☑ **E-Mail** olyayusupova498@gmail.co m

**B** Date Of Birth 05.12.1994

**&** County Istanbul

<sup>™</sup> Marital Status Married

➡ Driver Licence
B (Passenger car)

# Oguljemal Yusupova

I am a graduate of Moscow Medical College's Nursing Department, and I worked in the medical field for 1 year. However, due to my interest in computer science and technology, I wanted to gain more knowledge and expertise in this field. Therefore, I continued my educational journey in the field of software development. During this process, I acquired comprehensive knowledge about technologies such as C#, OOP, MS SQL Server, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Generic structures, ORM and Linq Queries, Entity Framework Core, Asp.Net Core MVC Application Development, Asp. Net Core Web API Application Development, and React. I am ready to bring my interests and skills in software development and technology to the business world. I am eager to contribute to various projects in line with the needs and to continually improve myself by using my curiosity for new technologies.

## EDUCATION

EDUCATION	
2017 - 2021	"Moscow Medical College No. 4", Moscow Nursing
09/2022 - 04/2023	Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer(MCSD) Infotech Academy, Istanbul C#, .NET Core, ASP.NET MVC, and Microsoft SQL Server - (200 hours)
03/2023 - 05/2023	React JS Front-End Web Application Development Education Infotech Academy, Istanbul (30 hours)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2020 - 07/2021	Moscow-Pushkino State Hospital / Moscow Nurse
	I worked as a nurse in the Anesthesia and Reanimation Department for a year.
04/2023 - 06/2023	Infotech Academy / Istanbul Intern Software Developer
08/2023	InfotechLab / Istanbul Junior Software Developer

### COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

Present Intremediate English Course(B2) / Just English

 $\mathbin{f Q}$  LANGUAGE

Turkmen, Russian, Turkish, English





